Just come outside for the night (Yeah)
Take your time, get your light (Yeah)
Johnny Dang, yeah, yeah
I been out geekin' (Bitch)
FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N (Yeah)
FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N
FE!N, FE!N (Yeah), FE!N, FE!N, FE!N
The career's more at stake when you
in your prime (At stake)
**** that paper, baby, my face on the
dotted line (Dot, yeah)
I been flyin' out of town for some
peace of mind (Yeah, yeah, bitch)
It's like always they just want a
piece of mine (Ah)
I been focused on the future, never
on right now (Ah)
What I'm sippin' not kombucha, either
pink or brown (It's lit)
I'm the one that introduced you to
the you right now (Mmm, let's go)
Oh my God, that bitch bitin' (That
bitch bitin')
Well, alright (Alright), tryna vibe
(I'm tryna vibe this)
In the night, come alive
Ain't asleep, ain't a—, ain't a—,
ain't-ain't
FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N
FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N
Syrup, woah, what?
What?
(Homixide, Homixide, Homixide,
Homixide)
What? (Yeah)
Woah, woah (Yeah, yeah)
(Homixide, Homixide, Homixide,
Homixide)
Hit, yeah, hold up (Yeah)
Yeah, I just been poppin' my shit and
gettin' it live, hold up (Shit)
Yeah, you try to come wrong 'bout
this shit, we poppin' your tires,
hold up (Shit)
Uh, hundred-round (Woah), feelin'
like I'm on ten
Playin' both sides with these hoes
(Hold up), shawty, I'm ****in' your
friend (Hold up)
I've been goin' crazy, shawty, I've
been in the deep end
She not innocent, uh, she just tryna
go
FE!N (Talkin' 'bout), FE!N, FE!N
(Yeah), FE!N, FE!N (Syrup, oh, oh,
what? Syrup)
FE!N, FE!N (Syrup), FE!N, FE!N, FE!N
(Oh, oh)
FE!N, FE!N (Talkin' 'bout), FE!N,
FE!N, FE!N, FE!N (Talkin' 'bout,
let's go)
I just been icin' my hoes, I just
been drippin' my hoes (Drippin' my
hoes)
This is a whole 'nother level, shawty
(Oh), I got these hoes on they toes
(Hoes on they toes)
I put the bitch on the road, she
tryna **** on the O, hold up, hold up
I got this ho with me, she tryna show
me somethin', hold up, hold up (Oh)
I got flows for days, these niggas
ain't on nothin', hold up, yeah (Oh)
Me and my boy locked in, you know we
on one, hold up, uh (Slatt, slatt)
We in the spot goin' crazy until the
sun up
You worried about that ho, that ho
done chose up (Slatt, bitch-ass)
Uh, pistols all in the kitchen, can't
give the zip code up, hold up, yeah
(Wow)
FE!N, FE!N, FE!N (Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Yeah)
Why the **** these niggas actin' like
they know us?
Double O, Cactus, yeah, we towed up
(Skrrt, skrrt), uh, yeah
Switch out the bag, these niggas get
rolled up, hold up (It's lit), slatt
Everything hit, hold up, everything
Homixide, Homixide (Homixide,
Homixide, Homixide, Homixide)
FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N, FE!N
(Homixide, Homixide, Homixide,
Homixide, Homixide, Homixide,
Homixide)